<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on The Metamodel Blog</title>
    <link>https://metamodel.blog/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on The Metamodel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://metamodel.blog/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>eBook</title>
      <link>https://metamodel.blog/page/ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</author>
      <guid>https://metamodel.blog/page/ebook/</guid>
      <description>This blog can be downloaded as an eBook using the ePUB or PDF format for offline reading using an e-reader:
  Most recent posts: ePUB / PDF
  All posts: ePUB / PDF
  These eBooks are automatically updated every time a new article is posted.
Each individual article may also be downloaded as an ePUB or PDF. Look for download buttons below the subtitle of each article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this blog</title>
      <link>https://metamodel.blog/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</author>
      <guid>https://metamodel.blog/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Metamodel: a model that consists of statements about models.
This is a blog about the language, science, and philosophy of predictive modeling. The aim is to be more whimsical than polemical, and mostly non-technical. The discussions will generally be about climate models, which are arguably the most complex models ever built. But models from related fields will make a guest appearance now and then. The discussions will frequently venture beyond science because prediction of long-term climate change is now so intertwined with the cultural milieu that it is impossible to discuss it within a purely scientific context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Policy</title>
      <link>https://metamodel.blog/page/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</author>
      <guid>https://metamodel.blog/page/policy/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Rights Commenting Privacy  Disclaimer This is a personal blog. The opinions expressed here are my own and do not in any way represent the official opinions of my employer.
Commenting To provide feedback on any post, you have two options:
  You can use Twitter to simply reply to the tweet announcing the blog post, which is displayed at the end of each post.
  If you don&amp;rsquo;t wish to use a tweet for your comment, or if your comment is too long, you can comment on the post at metamodel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://metamodel.blog/page/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>r@saravanan.us (R. Saravanan)</author>
      <guid>https://metamodel.blog/page/links/</guid>
      <description>Substack mirror of this blog  Personal
  Website
  Book page
  Twitter profile
  A few other climate modeling blogs
  Real Climate
  …and Then There&amp;rsquo;s Physics
  Serendipity
  Bryan Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s Blog
  Isaac Held&amp;rsquo;s Blog
  Podcasts related to climate prediction
 Deep Convection  Useful climate resources
 CarbonBrief.org Reporting extreme weather and climate change: A guide for journalists (WorldWeatherAttribution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
